NO ANIMAL WERE HURT DURING THE SET
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
- Salaimun Alaikum, Master Hasan.
- Alaikum Salam.
I've brought the goods.
- Salaimun Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
- What a good job, again.
- Eyvallah (thank you)
- Thank you.
- Do you have any coin, master?
Of course, sure I have.
Take it.
Thank you, son.
May Allah bless you.
Salaimun Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Mashallah (praise be)
May Allah bless him.
His father was martyred in the battle
of Inegol.
May Allah grant him with the
position of martyrs.
Amin.
Dervish Efendi, let me serve you food.
Thank you.
Very kind of you.
Ahmet, let's fill our stomach.
Ahmet!
Welcome, my Bey.
- Where is our Ertuğrul Bey?
- He is waiting for you back there.
My Bey, let me tie the horses.
Go reach your father.
Eyvallah. (thank you)
Father.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Bala, Hazal.
Yavlak Arslan haven't talked to me in
a while.
He hasn't asked me how I am doing.
If he is in this, I'm sorry for him.
If he is misled, I'm sorry for all the
Turkish community.
My Bey, Yavlak Arslan can't be mad
that much to betray us.
His sister is my Hatun.
Long paths, suffering years,
cruel enemies...
Obviously, those didn't educate you,
Dündar.
When did you make up with Hazal?
In the beginning of the summer, my Bey.
When Zöhre issue got too far...
Hazal gave up on her anger and
came to our tribe.
My Bey, we are running out of time.
Let us set off.
Let us search.
As long as one's time has not come,
he won't die.
If my Osman has still time...
He will destroy them.
Don't worry.
- Dündar.
- Yes, brother.
There is a lot going on, Dündar.
We will ruin them!
Inshallah.
First, we need to find the key.
What key, my Bey?
The key to open the snake nest.
We will find and ruin them.
Do you have the courage?
Can you really do it?
I can sacrifice myself for you, my Bey.
Hazal.
Hazal!
Come near your man.
Dündar.
Arrest Hazal.
Alps will take her to the caged tent.
Now!
I don't have time.
Ertuğrul Bey, what are you talking about?
What is my guilt?
Gündüz, set off.
They can ambush you.
Change your route.
Yes my Bey.
So is this what it is?
My Ertuğrul Bey who I trusted the most
wrote me off!
Ertuğrul Bey wants Osman Bey alone.
I was ordered this.
Our Bey of the Beys Yavlak Arslan wanted to
see Osman Bey, who shine in the battle.
Traitor dog.
Traitor dog!
Whose dog are you?
You have been trapped, Osman.
Don't push it.
Your bravery is replaced by your treason.
I will kill you myself.
Where is my father?
Where is he?!
Osman...
Ertuğrul's foolish son Osman.
Will it work, blacksmith, ha?
If your art let us down in the battle...
I will burn you in this heat.
If you don't find any track...
If you don't bring my Osman Bey back...
I will burn you in this heat, know that.
Things will get crazy.
If you are brave enough, kill me now.
Otherwise, I will kill you myself.
Don't worry, you are going to die
when you arrive there.
Who do you work for?
You will see Osman, we have a long way.
Take him!
Catch him! I want him alive!
My Bey, my brother.
Tell me if there is something
I need to know.
Before I go crazy...
please tell me.
Osman is your youngest nephew.
In our tradition, it's not about your age.
It is about how wise you are.
Our tribe, which we invested everything
for...
was about to collapse last year.
Why!
Forgive me, brother.
Have you been over your pride, Dündar?
Have you come to your senses?
Satan captured my soul. I did tawbah.
I appealed for mercy.
Fortunately.
Now, go to Söğüt.
Govern there for a while.
Don't come back until further notice.
Can I see Hazal before leaving?
I'd better get going.
You fool!
You should have aimed here, right here!
Osman Bey.
I'm coming, my Bey.
- Göktuğ.
- My Bey.
- My Bey, you are wounded.
- Brother, they will tire us a little.
Catch them!
They are coming.
My Bey, are you okay?
Come on my Bey, come on!
They are coming!
Let's go, my Bey.
You are wounded.
Let's go!
Hold on, my Bey, hold on.
Damn it.
Your death is coming, Osman!
Holy Caesar.
My first morning as a Lord.
I couldn't sleep.
Have a lot to do.
I need to start from the castle.
Our people are demoralized.
If I can't make my soldiers believe in
my dreams, everything will be wasted.
I learned this from you.
I have candidate to assist me.
I am very hopeful for him.
Hah! There he is!
Vladius.
Holy Caesar, allow me.
Do we have good news, Vladius?
You are rushing, Nikola.
Because I want to give victory
to my people as soon as possible.
We have signs of victory.
Your breakfast is ready, sir.
Delightful.
Congratulations.
I liked it. Whatever happened to us has
been because of our servants.
When is the flying fire coming?
I expect it tomorrow, Nikola.
Kayı Tribe will burn down.
My Bey, set me free.
I want to become martyr and see my brother.
We are one, brother.
Leave now, for the sake of my
martyr brother, my Bey!
Don't let him run away!
Göktuğ! Göktuğ!
Tie him up! Fast!
We will track him!
Ertuğrul Bey's arrival has been
sensational.
Look, even birds salute him.
A big one. Inshallah he doesn't go through
the grief of losing his Osman.
Bite your tongue!
Do you know about Gothic War, Vladius?
No.
A soldier who doesn't know history
is not complete.
Remind me in the evening, I'll tell you
about Caesar's struggle against Gothics.
What is that for? When I hear that,
will Ertuğrul's head be in my hands?
If you don't know history,
you can't win, Vladius.
Then it's worth hearing.
Look at those idiots!
They don't have pride!
Lose all those soldiers...
and still smile.
What an honour to see him, Vladius.
We came to agree with Osman,
we encountered Ertuğrul Bey.
Young man, if you want to be a Lord
in this land...
you have to know who you are going
to meet.
I like taking advice, Grand Turk Bey. Your
words are from the land of experience.
Your words are our earrings.
(your words are educational)
Do you want the captives?
We want our citizens.
What did you bring?
With this gold, you can't get even
our animals.
Not only a warrior, but also a trader.
I know how a trader feels.
I want to come to an agreement with
merciful Ertuğrul Bey.
I quitted showing mercy to cruels.
If you don't bring double this gold, your
captives will be dead.
Ertuğrul Bey, is this what Islam is?
You should thank us religion. Otherwise,
my Osman would wipe your heads out.
By the way, where is Osman?
Chopping off heads.
What you want will be
yours until tomorrow.
I want it before the evening azan.
You talked too much, oldish. You also didn't
stop talking when you killed my father
It's time I shut down your mouth.
We want peace, Ertuğrul Bey.
We want to fix our relationships which
Lord Alexis damaged.
How are things in Constantine?
Was the emperor sad when he heard about
the defeat?
He was sorry for the loss of both sides.
Tell your emperor to take example
of Caesars war against Pompeo.
Maybe it comes handy someday.
- Is this goat milk?
- It's sap.
Enjoy.
- How could you do it, Nikola?
- Vladius...
You bowed before my father's killer.
You gave him your regards.
You complimented him.
Vladius!
I've entered that tent
to negotiate with Gündüz.
I was going to say
"Either Kulucahisar, or war!"
What could I do when I saw that
old man standing in front of me?
Do you think Ertuğrul's return could
stop us from doing our duties, Vladius?
Vladius!
Years ago, Ertuğrul was going
to kill Karacahisar's lord.
My father stood up
to Ertuğrul to save him.
They fought. I saw everything from
where I hid in the castle.
I saw how my father
struggled to defend the castle!
He cut my father deep
with his every strike.
Just like the wounds in my flesh.
I wanted to scream. I wanted to
beg him not to kill my father!
But I couldn't, Nikola, I couldn't.
My father fell on his
knees with the strikes.
I still remember his eyes.
Then he turned to Ertuğrul and said...
" Don't you think you've
won a victory, Ertuğrul Bey."
"The war is just beginning."
But Ertuğrul just looked at him.
I see my father's death
every night in my dreams.
Every night.
I promise you.
Neither your father's, nor our
brothers' deaths will go unpunished.
We will crush them like rats.
We will be lions and
we will rip them apart.
Don't you think we've lost this war.
The war is just beginning, Vladius.
- Salaimun Alaikum, uncle Hasan.
- Alaikum Salam.
Where should they put them?
Here, my girl.
Bring them, Alps, come on.
Thank you, my girl.
You are welcome, uncle Hasan.
What happened?
Rats invaded Söğüt, you can
see dead rats in every market.
Stop! Don't touch it!
This is up to no good.
Wait for my word, no one
should touch the rats.
My Allah, I hope it's
not what I think it is.
Hazal is crazy right now.
When she gets out of the caged tent...
... I should calm her down.
Saltuk.
Find a craftsman, and ask
him to make a good wristlet.
As you command, my bey.
My Bey. Dündar Bey.
What is it, my girl?
My Bey, rats have invaded Söğüt.
Then snakes will have a feast, right?
Bring more bread.
But, most of the rats are dead.
May Allah preserve, if they are
carrying a disease, Söğüt is damned.
Saltuk, bring the people together.
We need to solve
this before it's too late.
My Bey, you are weary, I've heard you
liked Ayran food very much.
Would you eat some?
A Bey doesn't eat
alone in his table, my girl.
It's blessing would be gone.
Two of the folks are waiting outside.
Who are they.
I've invited blacksmith Davut and
potter Edis should you have questions.
Why them?
I thought, a black smith
knows about state's might...
... its valiant men, and a potter would
know about women who work the soil.
Then, I have a mission for you.
Anything you say, my Bey.
Make Hazal talk.
Get everything she knows from her.
Come, sit.
Who are you?
Have you seen a wounded Turk around here?
Do you know, do you know?
If you knew, would you understand?
- About what?
- About those who burn in flames...
... about those who sleep in ashes.
What are you talking about, madman?
Come on!
Go, beast, go!
Go, you beast, go!
Move, you beast!
You will taste it.
I swear, I swear you will taste it.
You will drink boiled waters!
You will only eat oleander,
and dine with the devil.
Don't do it, my Bey!
He is one of the Abdals,
we will be cursed!
If I ever see you again...
... I will take that head!
Death is from Allah. Death is from Allah.
Death is from Allah.
So, this mission is on
my beautiful girl, Bala.
You rushed to our help when
Zöhre tried to poison us...
... on my wedding day.
Thank Allah. It seems you had
breathe to take, words to say.
Osman is strong, and loves prosperity.
And he is enemies with
the ones who love prosperity.
Oh, my young Bala.
My beautiful girl, who doesn't
know what to say, what to ask...
... whose heart collided with her mind.
My Bala, who is crushed by the weight
of the mission given by great Ertuğrul.
You also know very well that if Osman...
... had died with poison, and
if I had killed Zöhre after that...
... then I would have
two birds with one stone.
I know that. But days pass...
... a person is just a human, they call
black to white today, then white to black.
Have you switched sides
in those past days, Hazal Hatun?
Finally, I see a woman worthy
of a Turkish Tent, a Turkish Bala.
My Bala, my beautiful girl.
I come from the Çobanoğulları.
If my intentions were of power...
... I would raze this Tent to
the ground when my Dündar...
... took Zöhre to his side.
Thank you.
I will send you food.
I only ask you one thing.
Tell my Ertuğrul Bey that...
... anything that comes from
him is welcomed by me.
But.
After he put me in this cage...
... and blamed me...
... for my nephew, Osman's trap...
... Hazal is just a dead body walking.
Our Tent is filled with life,
now that we saw you, my Bey.
I swear, this crazy Davut
is making all the iron talk!
How are my Alps wrists, their hearts?
Their hearts filled with life,
their wrist are powerful, my Bey.
Osman has made our Alps stay strong.
We have seen such disasters
while you were gone, my Bey.
We were very close to destruction.
Osman, Dündar, Gündüz couldn't stay strong
together. They have fallen into disorder.
Fortunately, Allah has smiled on us.
This is Bey's tent.
Wisdom and heart will talk here.
How are our sisters, our women?
Their hands weave,
their hearts build homes.
Our jugs are full, they
make their children happy.
Are there any who hits a woman,
a cruel on the land that I reign?
I swear, we had neither
heard nor seen such a thing.
I am happy to hear that.
Forgive me, my Bey, but despite all
others, why are you happy with this news?
We don't fear trouble,
we make our enemies bow before us.
But if our families are damaged,
if our men and women...
... succumbs to devil by
forgetting our mission...
... then we are doomed.
We shape our future in our families.
A nation who can't
hold its families together...
... will lost its future.
May Allah preserve.
My Bey, we have heard about our Osman Bey.
Which one of those jackals
could have done this?
Dogs will be dogs, about Osman...
... I trained him. He will destroy them.
I have no doubt.
Allah is with the good people.
Thank you.
Where did this man go?
What if that madman hid him?
They can't be far! They must
have gone to the forest!
You will not escape
me Osman! We are returning! Come on!
Where are you, Osman?
You will check under every stone! We will
not return without finding him!
Sir, to whom will you take him?
Why is he so important?
God's Whip wants him! If we can't find
and take Osman to that monster...
... he will eat us alive!
Spread out. You will
check under every stone.
We are not returning to
that hellpit without finding him! Come on!
You will not escape from me, Osman!
Beautiful fire, fire that
saved prophet Abraham.
May you help us.
Come on, Bey's son, time
to make the pain pretty.
Who did you bothered, that
you are wounded like this, my valiant?
The one who is eternal,
the one who gives life to all!
Göktuğ!
He's dressed like my father.
His clothings are the same.
What happened here?
Kuzgun trapped us. He was here too.
Where is Osman?
He is alive but wounded. They took
me hostage during the fight.
I couldn't follow them.
Kuzgun must know our
Bey well. He guaranteed himself.
Kuzgun is after our Bey
with his men. We should move now.
Gündüz Bey, if Yavlak
Arslan is behind this...
After Mongols and Byzantium...
... my father will not hesitate
opening the third frontier.
So, we should find Osman
and return to the Tent quickly.
- Are you alright?
- Yes.
Come on, Alps, we are moving. Come on!
Come on, brother, come on!
Justice forever!
Freedom forever!
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest!)
We are under the
mountain, Bey's son. We are safe.
I am not a Ghazi, but I know
how to take precautions.
I owe you my life.
Is it yours to begin with?
Thank you.
From where do you know me?
If we don't know you, wouldn't our eyes,
our ears, this hide on our backs be angry?
Marrow water, will make you strong.
They trapped us.
And you got out.
I need to sent wort to the Tent.
What about the Tent, Bey's son?
My father...
... they might have trapped my father.
Yavlak Arsland might
have attacked the Tent.
Bey's son! They would attack and they
would trap. It's devil, that's its job.
If the Tent has men and soldiers,
they would overcome.
Don't you worry,
first you need to be strong.
Is my wound deep?
Not as deep as Mecnun's.
How do you know about Mecnun's wound?
I treated him like I did to you.
You don't believe me, do you?
Suit yourself.
I will ask Mecnun.
Why is that?
I saved him from the tribes.
Right! You are in love too!
Lovers have everything!
A heart without love is like a stone!
That infidel!
He must be looking for us everywhere.
He will find us in the end.
I don't use weapons.
But I won't give you to them.
Tell me what you need,
I will tell them to get ready.
Thank you.
We will hunt them.
With our father, Jesus Christ's blessing,
are olive oils for our monastery ready?
My father prepared them specially for you.
Enjoy it.
Give my regards to master
Ariton. May the God watch over you.
You too, monk. You too.
Your figs are delicious.
You earned this. Take it.
Now take this, and continue trading.
Why don't you stay with your
father and help him in the kitchen?
I can't stay trapped between
the palace walls, sir.
Straightforward, I like it.
Your olives are good.
I sell them everywhere,
sir, not only here.
While the Turks take 1 in 5 for
taxes, you give 1 in 3, right?
Is that why our brothers and sisters
love trading with the Turks?
That's not the only reason, sir.
They never cheat.
People of İnegöl!
Your former Lord and his idiot
commanders have tortured you!
They have thrown you
to the Turks! Is that right?
That's right!
From now on, our brothers and sisters
will not be thrown to the enemy's arms!
Firstly, taxes in İnegöl...
... will be reduced to 1 in 5.
Now, return to your work, and work harder!
Work harder and earn more!
And never forget that we
are the true owners of this lands!
Nice move, you hit Turks
with their own weapons.
Not a move, that's the truth.
We are fighting for
these poor people, Vladius.
And it's just the beginning.
Thank Allah for this meeting.
May Allah makes us
together in the afterlife too.
Amin.
You sound eager to migrate early.
Migration is in our soul!
We've met with Osman.
His blood is like fast horses.
What about Savcı?
More cautious, more awake.
Oh, old man, looks
like Savcı is in your heart.
My Allah gave me 3 children.
My heart as a father
wouldn't love anyone more than the other.
How about your Bey's heart?
It's a world of test,
may the strong be winner.
May the one with the
heart be famous, it says.
You talked real, Ertuğrul.
What is the situation of the world?
It's a brownout.
At the end of the tunnel...
...we see light.
The seeds we planted in the Mongolian
army grows up.
They are onto each other.
We need to use this opportunity well.
If we save Anatolia...
...the realm of Turkestan will
stand up.
What should we do?
Dreaming of tomorrow.
First the dream, then the action.
You are right.
Victory is only real if it holds
even after you.
Yesterday is blurred. Today we are here,
tomorrow we won't be.
Who will sit in the warrior's tent?
You should make your mind, Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Start the trial.
Mashallah. It fits you well, Ahmet.
Bala Hatun.
We say that martyrs don't die.
-Yes, my valiant.
-If my dad didn't die...
...and he is alive. Please, tell him
to come now.
Ahmet Alp. From now, he will not come
to us.
-We will go to him.
-Let's go at once then.
Dear Ahmet, come.
Come.
Now that he is a martyr...
...he is in a very high position.
We need to get prepared to reach
his presence.
Is it even higher than a bey's?
It's even higher than a sultan's.
It's next to the Prophet's.
So, if you want to reunite with
your father...
...you need to be a hero like your father.
Gonca Hatun!
-What's happening here?
-We will get prepared to go to my father.
I can reunite with my father!
Ahmet.
Look, this horse is for you.
Bala. Things may go wrong at any moment
in Söğüt.
Trouble comes down on us like rain.
Protect us, my Allah.
May I enter, my bey?
My bey?
Ertuğrul Bey?
May I enter, my bey?
My bey?
Ertuğrul Bey?
Alps!
-Where is our bey?
-He was in the tent, Bala Hatun.
-Are you sleeping? Where is our bey?
-He didn't step out, Bala Hatun.
Then how did our bey got out?
Search everywhere, go!
Don't let anyone hear it.
They didn't leave him alone even in
his sleep.
Oh, let that tree get out of your chest
now, Osman Bey!
The secret is revealed.
The secret of Joseph's dream
is revealed.
It isn't destined for everyone to see that
dream. Aphorism of the world is in dreams.
I told you. Joseph saw the dream and
Father Jacob listened to the dream.
The stars in the sky, the sun in flames...
...and the shining moon kowtows
to Joseph.
Father was afraid, father shaken.
Nobody knew that Jacob was shaken.
Stars, sun, moon...
They would kowtow but...
Is it that easy?
Come on now, they said.
First, get thrown to the dump wells.
Get sold in the slave market,
sleep in dungeons.
Then, we will kowtow you.
Osman Bey, you are happy to have a dream
but you don't know what you will endure.
What you will have been through.
A man is only as great...
...as his dream.
If we saw a dream...
...if we are covered in blood...
...if we are seeking this path...
Both its rigor...
...and pleasure is good.
The one who is eternal...
What's happening?
A blessing to the tents, Master Davud!
You are goggling.
If the number grows,
your pouch grows.
Of course, it will, master.
But with halal coins.
Welcome.
Since you came out of my father's
tent like his daughter,...
...you must be Bala Hatun.
Ertuğrul Bey regards me as his
daughter.
I hope you will regard me as a sister
soon.
We are glad that Osman Bey brought a
fitting bride to him and...
...to our bey's blessed tent.
It was a long way. Take a breath,
and I'll bring you a cold ayran.
-Come. -My father, Osman, Uncle Dündar,
where are they?
I will tell you, Savcı Bey.
Let's get inside.
Everyone turns their eyes away
from me.
-What are you hiding?
-My bey, new goods are coming...
...if you allow me.
What's happening in the tents, Bala Hatun?
-Osman.
-What happened to my brother?
Speak, woman!
What happened?
-We need to find horses.
-Horse means a wish, bey's son.
Fulfilling a wish is a great talent.
-How much more?
-What is it?
Did it offend you to walk on foot,
bey's son?
A horse is the wings of a Turk.
Can a bird fly without its wings?
It can't.
Düldül was like that too.
It wouldn't breathe without Ali.
And Ali wouldn't go anywhere
without him.
I'm sad that I couldn't be the companion
of someone like Ali.
Isn't our path the same with Ali?
It is our path but are we companions
to walk in that way?
Eh, since dervishes don't ride horses
and swing swords, they sing like owls.
Troubles with everything.
Osman Bey, if you will walk with us,
you will bear our troubles.
The trouble you will bring is a grace.
My bey...
Mashallah, my bey.
Mashallah...
My bey...
Thank Allah for reuniting us, my bey.
Our reunion is like...
...the reunion of the ants.
Abdurrahman Gazi, even if our
faces stay away from each other...
...we remember each other's smell.
This smell will always bring us to
ourselves.
-Don't worry.
-Thank you, my bey.
I saw that you are all right, my bey.
As long as you are leading us,
I won't worry about anything.
How is your health, your welfare,
my bey?
I try to take care of the escrow well.
But I don't know if the escrow is
pleased with me.
They told me, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
I know what happened.
Know that your valour will be
spoken by everyone...
...tomorrow if not today.
Inshallah, my bey.
Inshallah.
Do you have any news from Bamsı Bey?
He finished his mission, my bey.
With your order, he will move back.
What about Selcan Hatun?
Selcan Hatun...
For a cure of her sickness...
...she picked many herbs from
many places.
She will be here with us soon.
Thank you.
I will need you.
Wait for my word at the place
we talked.
As you order, my bey.
They went this way!
Find their tracks.
Come on, my lions.
Yavlak Arslan's Hunting Tent
Yaren, my son.
Eat, Yaren.
Get stronger.
The war is soon.
Soon, all the tribes will
hear about...
...Yavlak Arslan's rooster.
Kayı Tribe's Bey, Ertuğrul, is coming,
my bey.
Yaren...
If the old wolf is coming, we
should protect you.
Take it away.
Who is accompanying Ertuğrul?
He is alone, my bey.
Sertaş.
I'm so handsome.
Yes, you are, my bey.
The lone wolf...
...come then.
Welcome, Ertuğrul Bey.
Welcome. Welcome.
-Salaimun Alaikum
-Alaikum Salam
Ertuğrul Bey, if you had
informed me of your arrival...
...I would want to host you in
my tents rather than here.
How did you know that I was hunting?
If we don't know what our enemies do...
...we can't know what our kins do, Arslan.
How is Kayı Tribe?
My sister Hazal, my brother in law Dündar,
the family...
...is all right, I hope.
Is your tent big?
Enough to fit me.
Do you have food?
No guest left hungry.
Is your door locked?
Welcome, Ertuğrul Bey.
I hope you will leave the same way.
The devil set a big game.
What do you think of, Savcı?
Indians have a game.
Shadow puppetry.
While the whole people...
...watch the shadows...
...they can't see the hand moving
the shadows.
So, you are saying that the trap on Osman
isn't the real plan?
They took my brother out of the tents
in a dishonorable way.
My father must've gone to Yavlak Arslan.
They reached their first goal.
But they have broken the mind
of the tents.
You say that they will have another
move, Savcı Bey?
Now one but a thousand ones maybe,
Bala Hatun.
Neither the dogs of Mongols, nor the
evil Nicola will stay idle.
They may attack today or tomorrow.
Can I enter?
Come.
-Salaimun Alaikum
-Alaikum Salam
Dervish of Sheikh Edebali.
He helps Osman Bey on important matters.
Thank you.
What's in the barrel?
It's an escrow.
What's happening, Savcı?
What does it say?
The evil Nicola is already on the move.
He brings ammunition from Byzantine.
He will attack.
We have to capture the ammunition.
Do you know what fruitfulness is, son?
Ertuğrul Bey, if the purpose of
your questions are to educate me...
...don't bother. My father gave me my
sword when I was five.
I know your father.
He was a capable man.
He was a brave man.
-Renown keeps the valiant alive.
-Treachery kills the traitor.
What's the news there?
My sister invited me many times but
we couldn't find time from jihad.
I put Hazal in the caged tent.
Don't even make a move.
I came here alone, as a father.
If this is your fatherhood,
how is your hostility, Ertuğrul Bey?
Your door isn't locked.
Instead of taking care of roosters,
chickens, worms...
...keep your front clean.
What are you saying, bey?
Who would dare to betray me?
You should know it.
You should see it.
Where is Kuzgun?
He went to support our veterans
in raid.
He lured Osman to a trap
and ambushed him.
What are you saying, my bey?
Kuzgun is my brother!
Don't meddle us to your
villany...
...in your tents.
It's my last words...
...your door isn't locked.
Take it as an advice.
The talent is to find the white
hair in the milk.
I should be going.
This way.
Be quiet.
Look where we found you.
And I was waiting or a force to lift
them to the donkey.
You came just in time.
Forget that and start speaking.
Keep in mind...
...this is how you set a trap.
My bey, hatun...
...is in the cage tent with
Ertuğrul Bey's words.
What they spoke is unknown.
Aah, ah, bey. He doesn't trust me.
So, is there news from...
...anyone else?
Nobody touches him!
Nobody!
Saltuk?
Where are those physicians?
We sent word to everywhere, my bey.
Someone must be coming.
May I enter, my bey?
Come, nephew!
Salaimun Alaikum, uncle.
Alaikum Salam
Welcome, Savcı.
Welcome.
In these dark days...
...you came as a light, my nephew.
Thank you, uncle.
I know what happened.
We will find the center of it...
...and remove it. Be at ease.
But today, I have more important
news for you.
Tell me. Whose dog are you?
Whose dog are you, huh?
Whose dog are you?
What happened?
Are you hurt, Osman?
You will speak.
Speak.
Speak!
Tell me!
Speak.
-Brother!
-My bey!
Brother!
-Thank Allah, my bey.
-Brothers!
Thank Allah, my bey.
My bey!
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah!
Göktuğ...
-How is your wound?
-I'm fine, my bey.
How are you holding up?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Thank Allah.
Brother.
Father was worried about you.
My father?
Brother?
Look at my Osman.
What a lion.
He isn't here but the soul
of my nephew is here.
Before the flying fire reaches
we must go and take it.
-Definitely.
-Nicola may be behind all this.
He must be the head of the
alliance of the evil.
Since the Emperor sent him personally,
he must be a capable devil.
But I can't leave here.
The disease spread a lot.
The people need us.
Two men are enough for me, uncle.
May your jihad be blessed, my valiant.
I've been longing for him.
Tell me, is he all right?
How is his health?
Good, brother, good.
Thank Allah, so good.
-Mashallah.
-He is waiting for you in the tents.
Osman.
Tell us what happened.
They entrapped us.
Factious dog!
Lena.
Hazal Hatun.
I know everything.
Anything from Ertuğrul Bey?
No one knows where he is.
He'll call my brother to account for.
I know Ertuğrul Bey very well.
If my brother...
can't convince him that he has nothing to
do with what happened to Osman Bey...
there'll be so much bloodshed.
Don't think about this now.
Let's talk a little bit.
I brought you some food.
What does Savcı say about it?
He's suspicious of Nicola.
I heard he is a lord.
Yes.
My father was a doctor in Karacahisar.
He treated him once.
I knew he was evil that time.
Hazal Hatun.
He's not here to be a lord.
He's the most important
commander of the Empire.
That's really difficult.
I'm glad you think like this.
You know, you're like my sister...
- I love you.
- I know.
You supported me after I married.
You taught me everything.
If it weren't for you...
What about Bala?
Have you met her?
Yes.
She looks like a good woman.
She is.
She is harmless.
As Ertuğrul Bey trusts her...
he charged her for the interrogation.
He treats her well.
But I know it's not a trust.
He suspects
me of what happened to Osman Bey.
What about you?
What do you think, Lena?
Your brother, Yavlak Arslan...
he is a smart Bey.
He's powerful.
If he wants to hurt Osman Bey, I know
that you won't let that.
Thank you.
Not just my brother...
they set a trap for Ertuğrul Bey too.
Savcı will listen to you.
Tell him that...
he must be careful.
There'll be lots of betrays in this land.
May Allah help us all.
Not a single arrow will be wasted.
Trap! It's a trap!
Allah is eternal!
Isn't there any news?
Don't worry, Nicola.
Today, we'll have
the ammunition that will end the Turks.
Here it is so hot, Vladius.
So hot.
You'll pay for it!
- Who are you?
- Your death.
When your death is this close, you
don't have to shout.
This is your lucky day. I don't have
anything to take from you.
I'll kill you fast.
We were waiting for gold.
This is black gold.
İNEGÖL CASTLE
What's new?
He's deaf. He won't hear
you, don't worry.
Yavlak Arslan's man trapped Osman.
Ertuğrul Bey raided Yavlak Arslan's tent.
Yavlak Arslan is cunning.
But he won't do it.
Who did it and why?
I want to learn it.
Your command.
- Is the "flying fire" here?
- On the way.
As Caesar said...
to the fools who bring us the victory!
Stay away!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
When will my grandsons, Aydoğdu
and Bayhoca will come?
Sabri Bey left them in Sinop.
So that they can learn how to trade.
My Savcı decided the best...
as always.
My Bey.
We worried about you.
What does Yavlak Arslan say about it?
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in, son.
Welcome.
I hope you have some good news.
They pack of this in the castle.
What's that?
The Mongols.
They brought it from China.
They call it "flying fire."
They used it in the
wars, conquering castles.
So, Nicola wants to take...
the castles we conquered with this powder.
I can go and kill that dog, father.
Nicola isn't someone to underestimate.
He's one of the
smartest evils I've ever met.
Every step of him is a consequence of
something bad.
We can't just stay like that.
We'll wait for Osman.
Don't we have a sword?
Why do we wait for him?
A sword that can stay with you...
is sharp.
If Osman is your brother, he is my son.
If I say patience...
I mean it.
It's what we need.
Do you understand me?
You heard Savcı Bey, right?
He can do everything for Osman.
I know that Osman would
do the same for Savcı.
Bala.
Osman and Savcı,
both can die for their loved ones.
And they're a death for their enemies.
Those who betray Osman Bey
will be punished by him.
Now...
we know what to do.
Make our work and forget the pain.
Settle in your tent first.
Does your Bey let you
stare at me like that?
Do you want me to cut your tongue?
You can't even drink water
without permission of your Bey.
Göktuğ.
Keep calm
Keep calm.
What are you thinking about?
My father.
First, I miss him.
Then...
he's always in my eyes, in my mind.
Separation is for coming together.
Our father waits for us.
Come.
Come on.
Göktuğ!
Don't!
We need this dog.
- Let me.
- Göktuğ! Don't!
Come...
and everyone sees how you
attack a man who is tied!
Let me go!
I'm not afraid of you, dog of Osman!
Göktuğ!
Göktuğ! Don't!
Allahuakbar. (Allah is greater.)
"Peace and Allah's mercy be upon you."
"In the name of Allah."
" My Allah, you let me
live till this age."
"You gave me dignity and power."
"Keep me in Islam until my last breath."
" Let me---
to--- my son...."
"I bear witness that there is no God except Allah"
"and I bear witness that Muhammad is the Messenger of Allah"
Here's your water, my Bey.
My Bey!
Ertuğrul Bey!
Father.
Alps! Come!
So, you want to fight.
- Come and see.
- Whose dog are you?
Talk!
Göktuğ! Stop!
Göktuğ!
Brother!
Stay away, Boran.
- Göktuğ! I said stop!
- Let me go, Boran!
When our sword isn't enough...
we fight with our minds.
I trust your sword and mind.
Thank you, Bey.
Thank you.
What are you doing?!
Alps!
What are you doing?
What kind of disrespect is this?
Göktuğ.
The cunning runs away.
The duty is yours, Göktuğ.
- May your holy war be blessed.
- Thank you, my Bey.
Thank you.
Come on.
Let's see what happens.
The best rooster!
Come here, boy.
Good boy.
The best rooster. The best of its race.
Shiny eyes, good beak.
The best of its race.
Wild as my soldiers...
smart as its owner.
The women show herself in bed, the
soldiers do in court.
Let's see which one will be my food.
My father Geyhatu says that
people who trust...
his wife and soldier so much
will end up in the grave.
Let's see it then.
My good boy.
- Good boy.
- Eat it.
Come on.
Come on, boy! Come on, boy!
Come on, boy!
Mashaallah!
Come on, boy! Good boy!
The best rooster!
What's its race?
Fezzan rooster.
Come on, silly animal!
Yes!
See it?
What's up with the Fezzan roosters?
When you throw the rooster...
if the rooster flutters and
looks up to the sky...
then it's ready for the fight
Yours look at the ground.
It'll be my dinner.
Don't lie to me, Yavlak Arslan.
- Tell me what the secret of it.
- I made it eat a hot pepper.
Walk!
Where's Osman?
He ran away.
He's after me.
He'll find me.
We know the owner of the cunning.
Come on!
Do you forge or do you
fight with the iron?
The tent is in sorrow.
I hope there's nothing wrong.
It's nothing good.
I brought water from the well. It'll
quench your thirst.
Give me.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Thank you.
Go around and check the tent.
- Bala Hatun loves you.
- Who do you think I am, Potter?
I won't be a talebearer.
Wow! Look at you!
My valiant!
He's such a valiant.
He's more of a man.
It's for you!
Ahmet, go check if they groom the horses.
May Allah protect all of us.
Father.
Thank Allah.
Osman...
is fighting with the snakes.
May Allah help him.
Our Osman will return here safe
and sound, Bey father.
He will.
Don't worry.
How are you, father?
Thank Allah.
I'm fine.
My Bey.
How will we leak in?
We won't.
We'll raid.
Brother.
Stay behind us and take measures.
Come on.
Come on!
What happened here, my Bey?
We thought Möngke was in this.
But there's something else.
It's a betrayal.
It's such a betrayal.
From now on...
I'm not the only target.
The trouble is bigger than we think.
They want to trap Kayıs.
- Be careful.
- Thank you, my Bey.
There's someone alive!
He's alive, my Bey.
Where's Möngke? Talk!
Talk!
Look at me.
Talk.
You saw everything.
Water...
Water.
Ayaz, bring water.
I'll give you the water and
you'll tell me everything.
Come.
Drink it.
Tell me everything.
Come on.
Tell me.
- Tell me what happened.
- Möngke...
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com